== Minute 1 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 1 ore.

== Minute 2 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.

== Minute 3 ==
Spend 2 ore to start building a clay-collecting robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 1 ore.
The new clay-collecting robot is ready; you now have 1 of them.

== Minute 4 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.
1 clay-collecting robot collects 1 clay; you now have 1 clay.

== Minute 5 ==
Spend 2 ore to start building a clay-collecting robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 1 ore.
1 clay-collecting robot collects 1 clay; you now have 2 clay.
The new clay-collecting robot is ready; you now have 2 of them.

== Minute 6 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.
2 clay-collecting robots collect 2 clay; you now have 4 clay.

== Minute 7 ==
Spend 2 ore to start building a clay-collecting robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 1 ore.
2 clay-collecting robots collect 2 clay; you now have 6 clay.
The new clay-collecting robot is ready; you now have 3 of them.

== Minute 8 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.
3 clay-collecting robots collect 3 clay; you now have 9 clay.

== Minute 9 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 3 ore.
3 clay-collecting robots collect 3 clay; you now have 12 clay.

== Minute 10 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 4 ore.
3 clay-collecting robots collect 3 clay; you now have 15 clay.

== Minute 11 ==
Spend 3 ore and 14 clay to start building an obsidian-collecting robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.
3 clay-collecting robots collect 3 clay; you now have 4 clay.
The new obsidian-collecting robot is ready; you now have 1 of them.

== Minute 12 ==
Spend 2 ore to start building a clay-collecting robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 1 ore.
3 clay-collecting robots collect 3 clay; you now have 7 clay.
1 obsidian-collecting robot collects 1 obsidian; you now have 1 obsidian.
The new clay-collecting robot is ready; you now have 4 of them.

== Minute 13 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 11 clay.
1 obsidian-collecting robot collects 1 obsidian; you now have 2 obsidian.

== Minute 14 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 3 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 15 clay.
1 obsidian-collecting robot collects 1 obsidian; you now have 3 obsidian.

== Minute 15 ==
Spend 3 ore and 14 clay to start building an obsidian-collecting robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 1 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 5 clay.
1 obsidian-collecting robot collects 1 obsidian; you now have 4 obsidian.
The new obsidian-collecting robot is ready; you now have 2 of them.

== Minute 16 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 9 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 6 obsidian.

== Minute 17 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 3 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 13 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 8 obsidian.

== Minute 18 ==
Spend 2 ore and 7 obsidian to start building a geode-cracking robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 2 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 17 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 3 obsidian.
The new geode-cracking robot is ready; you now have 1 of them.

== Minute 19 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 3 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 21 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 5 obsidian.
1 geode-cracking robot cracks 1 geode; you now have 1 open geode.

== Minute 20 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 4 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 25 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 7 obsidian.
1 geode-cracking robot cracks 1 geode; you now have 2 open geodes.

== Minute 21 ==
Spend 2 ore and 7 obsidian to start building a geode-cracking robot.
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 3 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 29 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 2 obsidian.
1 geode-cracking robot cracks 1 geode; you now have 3 open geodes.
The new geode-cracking robot is ready; you now have 2 of them.

== Minute 22 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 4 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 33 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 4 obsidian.
2 geode-cracking robots crack 2 geodes; you now have 5 open geodes.

== Minute 23 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 5 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 37 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 6 obsidian.
2 geode-cracking robots crack 2 geodes; you now have 7 open geodes.

== Minute 24 ==
1 ore-collecting robot collects 1 ore; you now have 6 ore.
4 clay-collecting robots collect 4 clay; you now have 41 clay.
2 obsidian-collecting robots collect 2 obsidian; you now have 8 obsidian.
2 geode-cracking robots crack 2 geodes; you now have 9 open geodes.
